I watched 20 Antifa militants help my assault suspect
escape into an Antifa safe house
that is one block away from the ICE facility.
It's where they're arresting, they're showering,
they're eating to continue this occupation.
I have staked out this safe house
and have observed shift changes.
This group is highly organized.
It is being funded through mutual aid groups,
and they have no plans of stopping.
The press is under attack,
and the White House press couldn't care less.
They're complaining about Trump waking them up on Air Force One
while brave reporters are documenting the dangers
of domestic terrorism in blue cities.
My question for all of you is, how would you feel?